(Penny:)Maybe. But this isn't
about them; it's about us.
(Penny:)It is.
It is about us.
(Penny:)And you know what
the best part is?
(Penny:)We took our time.
(Penny:)I mean, we met, we were friends
for a couple years,
(Penny:)then we got together,
and then we got untogether,
(Penny:)then we worked out
all our problems,
(Penny:)and now we know
everything about each other,
(Penny:)we can just go forward with
no surprises and no regrets.
(Sheldon:)Right.
No surprises.
(Penny:)And no regrets.
(Stuart:)Uh,
well, there-there's
one thing
(Leonard:)I feel I should tell you.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)You know, so we
can go into this
(Leonard:)with no secrets
between us.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Remember, uh,
a couple years back
(Leonard:)when I was on that research ship
in the North Sea?
(Penny:)Yeah.
Okay, well,
there-there was a
lot of drinking